Guide to the Rogan Jones Papers 1912-1983
Western Washington University, Heritage Resources
- Audio Materials, 1938-1970; undated; Series III
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, circa 1938-1970; Subseries 1
    - Grayhouse and Tobin re: Frye Memorial Public Art Museum, 1960 September 8 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Gargett Gold Mine, 1960 October 21 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - 1927 Day KVOS-KGMI Broadcast, 1961 August 2 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - 40th Anniversary Broadcast (2 Reels), 1964 November 16 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Rogan Jones' Presentation of a Stuffed Skunk to Virgil Barron, 1966 January (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Anniverary Show (KGMI 40th), 1967 November 15 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - KGMI 40th Birthday/Anniversary, 1967 November 15 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Fred Weihe Sr. regarding the Gold Mining Of Ruby Creek, 1970 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Olga Pattison (daughter of A. Eckland) - Coal Mines, Lone Jack Mine, 1970 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Dick J. Kink "Slovonians Of Whatcom County", 1970 January 12 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Peter Zuanich- Whatcom County Historical Society, 1970 February 9 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Jackie Lawson- interview with Mrs. Miriam Mathes, 1970 November 17 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Mary Peebles interview with Alfred Loop (edited), 1970 November 19 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Mary Peebles interviews with George McCush, Hobart Dawson and Alfred Loop (raw tapes 1 and 2), 1970 November 19 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Monroe McLauchlen (?) interview with Dr. Arthur Hicks, 1970 November 20 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Interviews with Dr. Arthur Hicks/Dr. Moyle Cederstrom/Ralph Neil, 1970 November 20; 1970 November 27 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Don De Marco interviews with Mr. Vaughn Brown / Mr. Walley Lindsley (master reel), 1970 November 19; 1970 November 30 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Interviews with Mrs. Miriam Mathes/Mr. Vaughn Brown/Mr. Walley Lindsley (edited), 1970 November 17; 1970 November 19;; 1970 November 30 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Gary Harrod Interview with Dr. Moyle Cederstrom (unedited), 1970 November 20 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - James Austin- Interview with G. W. Gannon (unedited), 1970 December 7 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Robin Probst- Interview with Miss Leona Sundquist, 1970 December 7 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - Dr. Arthur Hicks- Discusses post effects of Fisher's firing, 1970 December 9 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - Lynden Watts- Interview with Vernon Parberry on President Fisher, 1970 December 9 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Interview by John Stolpe with Dr. Paul Woodring discussing the Fisher firing and its aftermath, 1970 December 9 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - unidentified reel, undated (Box-folder 29/4)
  - Cassettes, 1970; Sub-series 2
    - Interviews with George Smith- and Bill Follis (2 tapes), 1970 November 17; 1970 December 1 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Hal Reeves, undated (Box-folder 29/5)
- Visual Materials, 1982; undated; Series IV
  - Photographs
    - People, undated (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Sailing Vessels (11 x 14 prints), undated (Box-folder 30/2)
  - Illustration: James R. Williamson, "City of Ships,", 1982 (Box-folder 30/3)